American Association for Labor Legislation Pamphlet File 5001 PAM
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 5, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Personnel of the Sectional Committee on Classification of Coal - M20, 1936; Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: The Mining Congress Journal, 1936; Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: Minutes Mining Standardization Correlating Committee, 1936; Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Item 11: A Consumers' Council for Coal, 1937; Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Item 12: United States Department of the Interior Bureau of Mines Information Circular, 1940; Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Author: C.A. Herbert
- Box: 5, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Names and Address of Operators Operating Mines on the Main Line of the Monogahela Railway, in West Virginia, and on he Scotts run Railway, Publication (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Note:, Publication (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: An Act to Amend etc. By Requiring that Certain Mines be Rock Busted, Publication (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: State Action for Mine Safety Some Basic Standards, 1937; Publication (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Committee on Coal Mine Ventialation National Standardization Division The American Mining Congress, 1925; Publication (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Twenty-Eighth Annual Convention The American Mining Congress, Publication (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Discussion of A. I. M. E. Technical Publication No. 975 "Recent Trends in Rock Dusting to Prevent Dust Explosions in Coal Mines" - By H. P. Greenwald, Publication (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Author: John E. Jones
  - Item 8: Report of Special Commission Appointed to Investigate Tuberculosis, 1909; Publication (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: Medical Inspection of Industrial Plants, 1908; Publication (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Author: C. T. Graham-Rogers
  - Item 10: Diseases and Disease Tendencies of Industries, The Pottery Industry, 1905; Publication (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Item 11: Factory and Workshop Act 1901, 1908; Publication (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Box: 5, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Factory and Workshop. Dangerous and Unhealthy Industries, 1908; Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Author: H.J. Gladstone
  - Item 2: Factory and Workshop. Dangerous and Unhealthy Industries, 1907; Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Special Rules for the Handling of Dry and Drysalted Hides and Skins, 1906; Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Compressed Air Illness With a Report of 3,692, 1909; Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Author: Frederick L. Keays
  - Item 5: Factory and Workshop. Dangerous and Unhealthy Industries, 1905; Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: Preliminary Tables (subject to correction) of Cases of Industrial Poisoning, Fatsl and Non-Fatal, 1908; Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: Factory and Workshop Act 1901, Notice of Poisoning, Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: The Detection and Treatment of Cases of Tuberculosis Among Factory Employees in Providence, 1907; Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Author: Frank T. Fulton
- Box: 5, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Mercurial Poisoning in The Industries of Great Britain, 1910; Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Author: Lindon W. Bates
  - Item 2: President Taft's Message, 1910; Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Bills Relating to Health Activities of the General Government, 1910; Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Physicians' Pocket Referednce to the International List of Causes of Death, 1910; Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Smallpox as an Industrial Disease or Accident, 1910; Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Author: Herbert E. Corbin
  - Item 6: Results of Ten years Notifications of Lead Poisoning, 1910; Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Author: Dr. T. M. Ledge
  - Item 7: Introduction; The Study of Occupational Diseases and Industrial Hygiene, 1910; Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: First National Conference on Industrial Diseases, 1910; Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Item 9: Certifying Surgeon's Report Upon Anthrax, Or Poisoning By Lead, Phosphorus, Arsenic, or Mercury, 1910; Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Item 10: American Bastiles, 1910; Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Author: Clarissa Olds Keeler
- Box: 5, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Factory Sanitation and Efficiency, 1911; Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Author: C. E. A. Winslow
  - Item 2: Chart showing number of Cases of Phosphorus Necrosis as reported by the Dental Examiners of The Diamond Match Co., 1910; Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Protection Against Occupational Diseases, 1911; Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: A Report to the Worshipful Company of Leathersellers, 1911; Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Author: Constant Ponder
  - Item 5: The Match Bill; Speech of Hon. John J. Esch of Wisconsin, 1911; Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Author: John J. Esch
  - Item 6: Report of Commission on Occupational Diseases to His Excellency Governor Charles S. Deneen, 1911; Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: Protection Against Occupational Diseases, 1911; Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Item 8: Industrial Diseases and Physicians, 1911; Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Item 9: Phosphorus Poisoning - Ivy, 1911; Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Author: Robert H. Ivy
  - Item 10: The Occupational Diseases of Modern Life, 1911; Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Author: W. Gilman Thompson
  - Item 11: Occupational Diseases; Case of Acute Lead-Poisoning, 1911; Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Notes: 1 Photograph
  - Item 12: Occupational Diseases; Case of Chronic Lead-Poisoning, 1911; Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Item 13: The Reporting of Industrial Diseases, 1912; Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Item 14: Mercury Poisoning in the Industries of New York City and vicinity, 1911; Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Author: Mrs. Lindon W. Bates
  - Item 15: Examination of Employes for Tuberculosis, 1912; Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Item 16: Lead Poisoning, 1912; Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Box: 5, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The Building Code and Tuberculosis Prevention, 1912; Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: The Building Code and Tuberculosis, 1912; Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Memorandum Submitted to the Committee on Building of the Board Aldermen, 1912; Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: Classification of Occupational Diseases, 1912; Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: The Reporting of Special Occupational Diseases in the Netherlands, 1912; Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Author: H. A. Van Ysselsteyn
  - Item 6: The Reporting of Special Occupational Diseases in the Netherlands, 1912; Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Item 7: Acute Reflex Disorders caused by the Cinematograph, 1912; Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Author: George M. Gould
  - Item 8: Le Charbon, 1912; Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Item 9: Anthrax, 1912; Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Item 10: Case of Industrial Poisoning Fatal and Non-Fatal Accidents, and Dangerous Occurences, 1912; Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Item 11: Buffalo's Progress Fighting Tuberculosis Our Third Year, 1912; Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Item 12: The Reporting of Industrial Diseases, 1912; Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Box: 5, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: The Health of the Worker, 1913; Publication (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: The Health of the Worker, 1913; Publication (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Second Report of Factory Investigation Commission; Wood Alcohol, 1913; Publication (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: One Lead Menace, 1913; Publication (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: Hygiene of the Boot and Shoe Industry of Massachusetts, 1912; Publication (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: Occupational Hygiene; read Before the Detroit Conference, Niagara Falls, 1913; Publication (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Item 7: Blazing the Trail, 1913; Publication (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Box: 5, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: What is Denatured Alcohol?, 1913; Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: The Tuberculosis Problem from the Sociological and Medical Points of View, 1913; Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Author: John R. Commons
  - Item 3: Experimental Laboratory of the New York State Commission on Ventilation and a Description of the First Year's Work, 1913; Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: Resolutions of the Special Commission on the use of Lead in the Ceramic Industry, 1913; Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: Beschlusse der Spezialkommission betr. Bleifrage in der keramischen Industrie, 1913; Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: Resolutions de la Commission speciale sur les intoxications saturnines dans l'industrie ceramique, 1913; Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: Anthrax: Its cause, prevalence, and prevention., 1913; Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 8: Handling White Lead, 1913; Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 9: Session 10/12/13 - 198 Legal Insurance of Workers against financial legal insurance of workers against financial losses resulting from occupation diseases, 1913; Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Box: 5, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Proposed Rules and Regulations Providing for the Sanitation of Living Quarters in Cannery Labor Camps, 1914; Publication (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Accidental Deaths by Drowning-Water Transportation, 1913; Publication (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: British Section, 1914; Publication (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: Industrial Poisons, 1914; Publication (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Item 5: Experimental Studies of the Effect of Various Atmospheric Conditions upon the Upper Respiratory Tract, Publication (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Item 6: Report on Ventilation and the Effect of Open Air and Wind on the Respiratory Metabolism, 1914; Publication (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Item 7: Consumption and Preventable Deaths in American Occupations, 1914; Publication (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Item 8: Federation Legislative Program, 1914; Publication (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Item 9: Occupational Diseases and Industrial Hygiene, 1915; Publication (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Item 10: Report of the Committee on Occupational Mortality, 1914; Publication (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Item 11: Occupational Anthrax, 1914; Publication (Box 5, Folder 19)
    Author: Devoto and Massarelli
  - Item 12: Case of Compensation of a Stone-Cutter, 1915; Publication (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Item 13: Report of the Committee to Obtain Full Information as to the Dangers Arising from the Presence Carbon Monoxide in Ordinary Illuminating Gas, 1914; Publication (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Item 14: Massachusetts Conference on Tuberculosis, 1914; Publication (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Item 15: An Ad-Interim Report of an Investigation of the Absense of Teachers of New York City Caused by Physical Disability, 1915; Publication (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Box: 5, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Institute for Tuberculosis Workers, 1916; Publication (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Author: Philip P. Jacobs
  - Item 2: National Conference of Commissioners on Uniform State Laws, 1916; Publication (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: Human Anthrax Report of an Outbreak Among Tannery Workers, 1917; Publication (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Author: Walter H. Brown and Charles E. Simpson
  - Item 4: Minutes Meetings of the Section on Social Insurance of the Commonwealth Club, 1918; Publication (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Item 5: An Outline of the Institute for Tuberculosis Workers, 1916; Publication (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Item 6: Are you in Business for Your Health?, 1916; Publication (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Item 7: Anthrax in Warehouses and Wharves, 1916; Publication (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Item 8: Anthrax Different Appearances of Anthrax on the Skin, 1916; Publication (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Item 9: National Conference of Commissioners on Uniform State Laws, 1916; Publication (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Item 10: Caution Effects of Chrome on the Skin, 1917; Publication (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Item 11: Aninlin Poisoning, 1916; Publication (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Author: William Lintz
  - Item 12: The Educational Function of Industrial Physicians, 1916; Publication (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Item 13: Some Theoretical and Practical Aspects of Industrial Medicine, 1917; Publication (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Author: Frederick L. Hoffman
  - Item 14: Memorandum No.1 Cutting Compounds as a Cause for Dermatitis and Wound Infections, 1918; Publication (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Author: Anna Baker Yates
  - Item 15: Final Report of the Committee on Industrial Diseases, Poisons, and Explosives, 1917; Publication (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Item 16: 1 GT Mono Section The Notifiable Diseases, Publication (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Item 17: Tuberculosis Examination of Soldiers at Camp Zachary Taylor, 1918; Publication (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Author: M.J. Lichty
  - Item 18: Reports to the Local Government Board on Public Health and Medical Subjects, 1917; Publication (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Item 19: Tuberculosis: An Industrial Accident, 1917; Publication (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Author: John B. Hawes
  - Item 20: An Inquiry into the Prevalence and Aetiology of Tuberculosis among Industrial Workers, with special reference to Female Munition Workers, 1918; Publication (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Box: 5, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Sanitation for Painters, 1922; Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
    Author: G.W. Thompson
  - Item 2: Memorandum on Industrial Lead Poisoning, 1921; Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: Anthrax Problem in Massachusetts, Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
    Author: Stanley H. Osborn
  - Item 4: Fifth Draft of a Uniform Occupational Diseases Act, 1920; Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Item 5: Prevention of Anthrax Among Industrial Workers, 1921; Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Item 6: Weekly Bulletin, 1922; Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Item 7: Statistician's Department, Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Item 8: Report of the A.C.S. Committee on Occupational Diseases and Hazards in Chemical Trades, 1924; Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Item 9: Tentative List of Occupational Diseases, 1923; Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Item 10: Report on the Incidence of Silicosis in the Pottery Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Item 11: Forty-Two Occupational Disease Hazards in One Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Item 12: Wisconsin Labor Statistics, 1930; Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Item 13: Educating for Longer Life, Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Item 14: Film List, 1928; Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Item 15: The Antifreeze Methanol Hazard, 1931; Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
    Author: Max Trumper
  - Item 16: Progress Toward Prevention of Occupational Diseases, 1928; Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Item 17: Report on the Occurrence of Silicosis among Sandstone Workers, 1929; Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
    Author: Dr. C.L. Sutherland and Dr. S. Bryson
  - Item 18: Rock Drilling, Sand Blasting, and Rock Crushing, 1929; Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Item 19: Effect of Abnormal Air Condition on Mine Workers, 1930; Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Item 20: Effect on Workers of Air Conditions, 1931; Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Item 21: Division of Industrial Hygiene, 1932; Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
    Author: James D. Hackett
  - Item 22: Industrial Code Removal of Dust, Gases, and Fumes, 1930; Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Item 23: Minutes of Meeting of Advisory Committee on Rock Drilling, Sand Blasting and Rock Crushing, 1931; Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Item 24: The Engineering of Occupational Diseases by Plant Equipment and Operation, 1932; Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
    Author: Reuel C. Stratton
- Box: 6, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Silicosis Project, 1936; Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Designated Special Committees Personnel and Duties, 1936; Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Silicosis, 1936; Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Author: Emery R. Hayhurst
  - Item 4: Proceedings at National Conference on Silicosis, 1936; Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: The Development of the Synthetic Textile Fibre Industry in the United States and Some Associated Health Hazards, 1936; Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Author: Dr. Alice Hamilton
  - Item 6: Industry as a Source of Disease, 1937; Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Some Facts on Compensation Costs with Special Reference to Inclusion of Occupational Diseases, 1937; Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Author: Henry D. Sayer
  - Item 8: Some Essentials in Occupational Disease Legislation, 1936; Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Trauma and Tuberculosis, 1936; Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Author: J.A. Goldberg
- Box: 6, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Report of a Study of the Foundry Industry in North Carolina, 1938; Publication (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Author: M.F. Trice and H.F. Easom
  - Item 2: Introduction, 1939; Publication (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Author: Gifford S. Cochran
- Box: 6, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Majority and Minority Reports to the Governor and Council, 1939; Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Meeting on Occupational Health Hazards, 1940; Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Wisconsin Physical Examination Program, 1939; Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Occupational Health Hazards in Massachusetts Industries, Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: A Seven Million Dollar Itch!, 1941; Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Author: Joseph Stifter
- Box: 6, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Tuberculosis Among Wage Earning Classes Tends to Decrease, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Tuberculosis Problem in a Working Place, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: To the Grewsome Record of Convictions, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Massachusetts General Hospital Industrial Poisons, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Industrial Poisoning in Pennsylvania, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Occupational Diseases- Real and Supposed, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Compensation for Industrial Diseases: International Standards, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Author: Leifur Magnusson
- Box: 6, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Proposed Rules relating to the Control of Silica Dust in Rock Drilling, 1937; Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Mortality 1897-1906 Figures Taken from one Industrial Insurance Co., Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Occupational Diseases- Real and Supposed, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: A Study of the Diseases of Lead Workers, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Factory Sanitation and Efficiency, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Author: C.E.A. Winslow
  - Item 6: The Lead Menace, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Author: Gordon Thayer
  - Item 7: Lead Poisoning in the United States, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Box: 6, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Industrial Diseases Rapid Reference Manual, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Silicosis, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Lead Poisoning Information for Workmen and Directions for Prevention, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Industrial Poisoning by Gases of Arsenic and Phosphorus, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Author: John Glaister
  - Item 5: Occupational Diseases- Real and Supposed, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Memorandum on Tri-State Silicosis Investigation, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: The Examination of Employees for Tuberculosis, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Author: Theodore B. Sachs
  - Item 8: Ellie's Wishes, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Author: Winifred Hathaway
  - Item 9: Industrial Diseases, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Author: Fred Merk
  - Item 10: What the War has done to stamp out Venereal Diseases, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: V.D. U-Boat Number Thirteen, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: Silicosis Claims A New Problem in the Insurance Field, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Author: Frederick S. Kellogg
  - Item 13: Ankylostomiasis and the Mining Industries, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Author: Sir Thomas Oliver
  - Item 14: The Status of Workmen's Compensation Legislation, 1917; Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Author: August Belmont
  - Item 15: Tri-State U.S.A., Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 16: Should Society Protect the Hleath of its Workers?, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 17: Illustration of What is Meant by Industrial Tuberculosis, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 18: Some Dust Hazards of Industry with Particular Reference to Silicosis, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Author: Frederick Willson
- Box: 6, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Open Shop Bulletin No. 26, 1930; Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Anti-Union Employment Contracts, 1929; Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Author: E.R. Burton
  - Item 3: Study of Forms of Employee Organizations and of Employment Contracts, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Yellow Dog Contract Seems Doomed in Three States, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Author: International Labor News Service
- Box: 6, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Message of Governor Fred M. Warner to the Forty-fifth Legislature of Michigan, 1909; Publication (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: The Prison Labor Question in Rhode Island, Publication (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Resolution Adopted by the Southeastern Industrial Allocation Conference, Publication (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Report of the Convict Labor Committee, 1909; Publication (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Report of the Special Committee on Prison Labor, 1908; Publication (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Convict Made Goods, 1909; Publication (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Report of Special Committee, Publication (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: Ohio Special Report on Prison Labor, 1910; Publication (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: The Importance of the Prison Labor Problem, 1910; Publication (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Box: 6, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Twentieth Century Prison Policy, 1932; Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Initial Conference Committee on Allocation of Prison Industries, 1924; Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Report of Annual Meeting, 1938; Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Notes: April 11, 1938
  - Item 4: States' Use of Prison Made Goods, 1926; Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Resolution Adopted by the Eastern Prison Industrial Allocation Conference, 1924; Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: An Educational Program for New York State's Penal System, 1932; Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Notes: January 1932
  - Item 7: Nouvelle Organisation des Prisons, 1939; Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: The County Jail, 1914; Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Author: W.H. Oates
- Box: 6, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Delegates Present at Conference of Executive Offices of National Organizations Interested in Public Health Problems, 1913; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Minutes First Conference of Executive Officers of National Organizations Interested in Public Health Problems, 1913; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Surgical Diseases of Umbilicus, 1911; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Author: Thomas S. Cullen
    Notes: Chicago